themedy.com 2012-05-04

# Privacy Policy - Themedy

(last update: Mar 2011)

### Information we gather

The following information is gathered from our website visitors:

IP address  
Our visitor tracking system will store details about your location and certain anonymous system configurations such as screen resolution.

Registration Information  
You will provide us information about yourself, your firm or company, and your practices when you purchase [Themedy](http://themedy.com/) products and services, register for forum support, or register for email newsletters and alerts.

Email Information  
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

### How we use the information we gather

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to this website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in each such email.

### The people that are given access to this information

Your personal information is accessible by staff members of [Themedy](http://themedy.com/).com

We use third parties to facilitate our business, including, but not limited to, sending email and processing payments. In connection with these offerings and business operations, these third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with those business activities.

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions.  
We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution.

If it becomes necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

### The security measures we have in place to protect your personal information

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Some of the information you may enter on this site may be transmitted securely via Secure Sockets Layer SSL, 128 bit encryption services. Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP.

### Our use of cookies

Our website makes use of cookies which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website.

Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalise your experience of our website.

Additionally, 3rd party advertisers on our site may use cookies for tracking purposes.
